http://www.corecon.com/privacy-policy

see online demo
CORECON TECHNOLOGIES PRIVACY POLICY Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to Corecon Technologies, Inc and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Corecon Technologies Inc include Corecon’s Corporate Website (www.corecon.com), Corecon's Cloud-based Software Suite (app.corecon.com), TeamLink Portal (teamlink.corecon.com) and CoreconLink utilities.Corecon develops construction estimating and project management software and uses a Software as a Service (SaaS) deployment model. By using Corecon’s website and services, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationCorecon may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Corecon. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Corecon’s website and services.Corecon encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Corecon so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Corecon is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of Corecon’s website and services.Use of your Personal InformationCorecon collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.Corecon may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Corecon and its affiliates. Corecon may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Corecon does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.Corecon may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Corecon, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Corecon may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Corecon, in order to determine what Corecon services are the most popular.Corecon will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Corecon or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Corecon; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Corecon, or the public.Security of your Personal InformationCorecon secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.Opt-Out & UnsubscribeWe respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Corecon by contacting us here:Email: information@corecon.comPhone: 714-895-7222Changes to this StatementCorecon will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Corecon encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Corecon is protecting your information.Contact InformationCorecon welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Corecon has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Corecon at:Corecon Technologies, Inc 5912 Bolsa Ave, Suite 109 Huntington Beach, California 92649Phone: (714) 895-7222 Email Address: information@corecon.comDate Last Modified: 11/16/2016
SEE WHY CORECON IS THE INDUSTRY CLOUD CONSTRUCTION SOFTWARE GOLD STANDARD
request a demo
CONTACT US1.866.258.6698sales@corecon.com
Our CompanyContact UsBlogPrivacyTerms of Use
login
request a demo
© 2020 Corecon Technologies, Inc | All rights reserved | Website designed by Olive Street DesignThird party trademarks, logos and trade names appearing on the site are the property of their respective owners.
Share by:
